Guide to the Naegele Outdoor Advertising records, 1978-2002 and undated RL.11324
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Naegele Slides, 1982-1990 and undated; 3
  - Religion, holidays, undated (Box 90)
  - Restaurants, undated (Box 90)
  - School Kids Art Contest, 1990 (Box 90)
  - Shopping, retail, undated; 2 folders (Box 90)
  - Small towns, undated (Box 90)
  - Spin, undated (Box 90)
  - Spinnaker, undated (Box 90)
  - Sporting goods, undated (Box 90)
  - Sports and fitness, undated; 2 folders (Box 90)
  - Streets, buildings, undated (Box 90)
  - Thornton/Odyssey, undated (Box 90)
  - Title slides for presentations, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 90)
  - Travel, vacations, undated (Box 90)
  - Trent/Jedco, undated (Box 90)
  - Unused slides, 87 presentation, 1987; 2 folders (Box 90)
  - U.S. Olympics, 1987 (Box 90)
  - Utilities, undated (Box 90)
  - Vehicles, undated (Box 90)
  - Vehicles, undated; 2 folders (Box 91)
  - Victoria Place, undated (Box 91)
  - Vision, Optometrists, undated (Box 91)
  - Voting, citizenship, undated (Box 91)
  - WCTI 12 Live News, undated (Box 91)
  - Word of Faith/Naegele Christmas, 1989 (Box 91)
  - Wrightville Marina, undated (Box 91)
  - WRCM, Subway, undated (Box 91)
  - WWQQ Shell Island, undated (Box 91)
  - Z103, undated (Box 91)
  - Unsorted slides, undated; 5 folders (Box 91)
  - Unsorted slides, undated; 3 folders (Box 92)
  - Unsorted slides, undated (Box 93)
- Naegele Photographs, 1978-1991 and undated; 4
  - Advertising, undated (Box 93)
  - Alcoholic beverages, 1981-1990 (Box 93)
  - Alcoholic beverages--Beer, 1981-1990 (Box 93)
  - Alcoholic beverages--Beer--Budweiser, 1984-1990 (Box 93)
  - Alcoholic beverages--Beer--Miller, Miller Lite, 1980-1985 (Box 93)
  - Alcoholic beverages--Maker's Mark, undated (Box 93)
  - Alcoholic beverages--Wine, 1985-1990 (Box 93)
  - Announcements, Public service, undated; 2 folders (Box 93)
  - Apparel, 1978-1990; 4 folders (Box 93)
  - Automobile dealerships, undated; 2 folders (Box 93)
  - Automobile dealerships--Don Kimball, undated (Box 93)
  - Automobile parts, supplies, services, 1978-1990; 2 folders (Box 94)
  - Banking, finance, undated (Box 94)
  - Beverages, undated (Box 94)
  - Beverages--Sun Drop, undated (Box 94)
  - Billboard details, undated (Box 94)
  - Creative contest, 1987-1989 (Box 94)
  - Christmas, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 94)
  - Exhibitions and expos, 1987-1989 (Box 94)
  - Festivals, shows, tours, 1987-1989 (Box 94)
  - Food, undated (Box 94)
  - Hurricane damage, undated (Box 94)
  - Location shots, undated (Box 94)
  - Medical, health services, 1983-1990; 3 folders (Box 94)
  - Moving and storage, 1987-1989 (Box 94)
  - Music, theater, 1979-1990 (Box 94)
  - Naegele self-promotion, undated (Box 95)
  - Outdoor, beach shots, undated (Box 95)
  - People, outings, undated (Box 95)
  - Radio, television stations, 1982-1990; 6 folders (Box 95)
  - Real estate, 1983-1990; 3 folders (Box 95)
  - Real estate--Atlantic Towers, undated (Box 95)
  - Real estate--Bland and Associates, undated (Box 95)
  - Religious, undated (Box 95)
  - Resorts and entertainment, undated (Box 95)
  - Resorts, camps and theme parks, undated (Box 95)
  - Restaurants, 1979-1990; 4 folders (Box 96)
  - Restaurants--Barbecue, 1981-1989 (Box 96)
  - Restaurants--Burgers and fast food, 1979-1990 (Box 96)
  - Restaurants--Chinese, Asian, 1978-1989 (Box 96)
  - Restaurants--Kanki, undated (Box 96)
  - Restaurants--McDonald's, 1981-1990 (Box 96)
  - Restaurants--Mexican, 1981-1990 (Box 96)
  - Restaurants--Pizza, Italian, 1982-1990 (Box 96)
  - Restaurants--Seafood, 1978-1989 (Box 96)
  - Restaurants--Steakhouses, 1978-1989 (Box 97)
  - Retail and miscellaneous, 1980-1989 (Box 97)
  - Retail--Armstrong, undated (Box 97)
  - Retail--Barnes Diamond Gallery, undated (Box 97)
  - Retail--Benjamin Moore/Owen Paint, undated (Box 97)
  - Retail--National Outlets, undated (Box 97)
  - Retail--Reed's Jewelry, Rolex, undated (Box 97)
  - Sales and management conference group photograph, 1961 (Folder 1)
  - Sports and fitness, 1979-1991 (Box 97)
  - Staff, people, other, undated (Box 97)
  - Telephone services, 1985-1989 (Box 97)
  - Tobacco, undated (Box 97)
  - Video rental, movies, 1987 (Box 97)
  - Zoo, circus, 1987 (Box 97)
  - Unsorted, damaged photographs, undated (Box 97)
  - Unsorted photographs, undated; 2 folders (Box 102)
  - Negatives, 1978-1991 (Box 98)
- General Files, 1980-1992 and undated; 5
  - A Brief Look at the Naegele Markets, 1986-1987 (Box 99)
  - Alternate Copy Suggestions, 1982-1984 (Box 99)
  - ARRCO Button Co. catalog, 1984 (Box 99)
  - Associated Posters--"Headlines", 1986 (Box 99)
  - Associated Posters--Promotional brochure, undated (Box 102)
  - Bald Head Island Vacation Guide, 1989 (Box 99)
  - Billboard program and order forms, undated (Box 99)
  - Cape Fear Area Council--"Tide" Boy Scouts newsletter, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Chevrolet Outdoor Program Market Test, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Christmas cards, 1986 (Box 99)
  - Chrysler--Dodge, Plymouth Outdoor Billboard Designs, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Clipper--Clip Bits, 1992 (Box 99)
  - Compton--Outdoor Production brochure, undated (Box 99)
  - Creative designs, Naegele Memphis, 1982 (Box 99)
  - Expense reports, 1984-1985 (Box 99)
  - Formetco--Coffee Break, 1991 (Box 99)
  - Holiday billboard designs, 1987 (Box 99)
  - Inside Outdoor, 1987-1990 (Box 99)
  - Institute of Outdoor Advertising, 1980-1983 (Box 99)
  - Institute of Outdoor Advertising--Sales Opportunities, 1981 (Box 102)
  - Legal Services of the Lower Cape Fear--Data sheet, undated (Box 99)
  - Mark Hoge memoir, 1988 (Box 99)
  - Masonboro Island, 1989 (Box 99)
  - Maxim Lighting catalog, 1990 (Box 99)
  - Mazda RX7 brochure, 1989 (Box 102)
  - Memos and miscellaneous papers, 1981-1992 (Box 99)
  - Naegele Outdoor stamping machine, undated (Box 102)
  - The National Group--Idea Tank poster, 1985 (Box 87)
  - National Imprint Corporation--Political Campaigning catalog, 1982-1983 (Box 99)
  - New accounts, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Outdoor advertising surveys, North Carolina, 1981 (Box 100)
  - Poster sign order forms, undated (Box 102)
  - Posting cards, 1989 (Box 100)
  - Rates and Coverage books, 1986-1990; 5 folders (Box 100)
  - Rate cards, 1985-1990 (Box 100)
  - Restaurant News and Interiors, 1984 (Box 100)
  - Robert Keith and Company--The Third Dimension (3-D billboard structures), undated (Box 100)
  - Sales Upbeat (periodical), 1991 (Box 100)
  - Selling Small Markets--Wilmington, undated (Box 102)
  - Sign Ordinance and recommendations, Wilmington NC, 1990 (Box 100)
  - Solaray by Eye Catchers, 1986; 2 folders (Box 101)
  - Traffic Audit Bureau, bylaws and memo, 1981 (Box 101)
  - United/UAI--Christmas poster designs, 1984 (Box 101)
  - United/UAI--Creative binder "Outdoor Teasers", 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 101)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1980-2000 and undated; 6
  - City Junction paint mechanical memo and image, 2000 (Box 103, Disk RL11324-FL3-001)
  - Outdoor, The New Messenger, Produced by Naegele Outdoor, with Hugh Downs, mini DV, TRT 18:37, 1980 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11324-MDV-001)
  - Outdoor, The New Messenger, Produced by Naegele Outdoor, with Hugh Downs, VHS, TRT 18:37, 1980 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11324-VHS-001)
  - Selected Solaray Billboards by Eye Catchers, VHS, undated (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11324-VHS-002)